[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can create this
您可以创建此
rocket logo design using inkscape but
火箭标志设计使用Inkscape BUT
before we get started if you'd like to
在我们开始之前，如果你愿意
learn more about how inkscape works be
了解有关Inkscape如何工作的更多信息
sure to check out my inkscape master
一定要看看我的Inkscape大师
class
班级
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where i go over all of the tools and
在那里我检查了所有的工具和
features in inkscape
Inkscape中的功能
and i explain what they are and
我解释了它们是什么，
demonstrate how they work i'll put a
演示它们是如何工作的，我会放一个
link in the description of the video if
视频描述中的链接，如果
you want to check that out
你想去看看吗？
so to get us started here in inkscape
为了让我们从Inkscape开始
the first thing i want to do is just set
我想做的第一件事就是设定
up
向上
the uh the screen here so that we're all
呃，屏幕在这里，所以我们都
working with the similar layout i want
使用我想要的类似布局
to come up here to where it says view
来到这里，看到它说的景色
make sure we have custom selected i'm
确保我们已自定义选择了我是
going to come over here to where it says
会走到这里，上面写着
zoom and i'm going to zoom in at one to
ZOOM和我要在一点放大到
one
一
and then i'm going to open up the align
然后我要打开Align
and distribute menu with this button
并使用此按钮分发菜单
over here or you can press ctrl
在这里，或者你可以按ctrl键
shift and a i want to have last selected
Shift和我想要上次选择的
chosen from this relative two
从这两个亲属中选择
and then i want to open up the fill and
然后我想打开填充物
stroke menu which is over here you can
笔划菜单在这里，您可以
click on that or you can press ctrl
单击该按钮或按Ctrl键
shift and f to open that up so what i'm
Shift和f来打开它，所以我
going to do first is i'm going to create
首先要做的是，我要创建
a circle that is going to
一个即将到来的圆圈
encapsulate the entire design so let me
封装了整个设计，所以让我
grab the circles and ellipses tool
抓取圆形和椭圆工具
i'm going to hold ctrl and shift on the
我要按住Ctrl键和Shift键
canvas i'm going to hold ctrl and shift
画布我要按住Ctrl和Shift键
and click and drag on the canvas to
并在画布上单击并拖动以
create a perfectly round circle like
创建一个完美的圆形，就像
that
那
now let me grab the select tool let me
现在让我拿起选择工具让我
move this over what i want to do now is
把这个移到一边我现在想做的是
just bring down the opacity of this a
只要把这个的不透明度降下来
little bit i'm going to take the opacity
我要把不透明的部分
bring that down roughly in half we're
把它降低大约一半，我们是
going to want to be able to see through
会想要能够看透
what we're working with
我们正在处理的问题
as we go through this tutorial one other
在我们学习本教程的过程中，一个接一个地
thing i wanted to
我想做的事
i forgot to mention up here where it
我忘了在这上面提到它在哪里
says enable snapping make sure you have
建议启用捕捉功能以确保您拥有
this turned off for the duration of this
在此期间，此功能处于关闭状态
tutorial or for now anyway so
教程或现在，无论如何都是这样
go ahead and disable that i think by
继续并禁用我认为的
default it's enabled so just go ahead
默认情况下它已启用，因此请继续
and
和
disable that so we have our circle right
禁用它，这样我们就有了正确的圆圈
there what i want to do is just
我想要做的就是
duplicate this circle by hitting control
按下Ctrl键复制此圆
d
D
i'm going to make this copy green and
我要把这份复印件做成绿色和
i'm going to hold ctrl and shift and
我要按住Ctrl和Shift键，然后
scale this down a little bit
把这个缩小一点
and what i'm going to do here is i'm
我要在这里做的是我
going to create some plumes of smoke
会产生一些烟柱
going towards the bottom of the uh
走到了呃底部
the bottom of the design here let me
这个设计的底部让我
show you here we're going to create this
向您展示我们将在这里创建这个
segment right here using a bunch of
就在这里使用一堆
individual circles so let me
个人圈子，所以让我
minimize that i'm going to make this one
最小化我要做的这件事
a little bigger
再大一点
put this right about here duplicate this
把这个放在这里复制这个
by pressing ctrl d
通过按ctrl d键
make this one a little smaller again
把这个再改小一点
holding ctrl and shift while scaling
缩放时按住Ctrl和Shift键
this down to lock the proportions
这是为了锁定比例
ctrl d to duplicate again hold ctrl and
再次按Ctrl d复制按住Ctrl和
shift make this one a little smaller
换个档位，把这个做小一点
maybe i'll put this over here
也许我应该把这个放在这里
put the medium size over here on the
把中号的放在这边的桌子上
left put the smaller one right here like
左边把小一点的放在这里，就像
that
那
maybe make this a little smaller
或许可以把这个做小一点
duplicate this by hitting ctrl d bring
点击Ctrld Band复制此命令
this over here
这就是这里
duplicate this one put this over here
复制这个，把这个放在这里
maybe like that and right there that's
也许就像这样，就在那里
about what i'm looking for i want to
关于我正在寻找的东西，我想
have this
拿着这个
this is going to represent the the the
这将代表着
clouds are like the exhaust coming from
云就像尾气一样从
the rocket here
这里的火箭
and uh what i want to do now is i just
我现在想做的是我只是
want to make sure the bottom portion of
我想要确保底部的
this design is covered in as well so i'm
这个设计也包括在内，所以我
going to duplicate some more of these
我要复制更多这样的东西
circles
圆圈
and just scale them up so that it's
只是把它们放大，这样它就
covering the entire portion of the
覆盖了整个
design as you can see i'm stamping these
如你所见的设计我正在盖章
circles by pressing spacebar as i move
在我移动时按空格键进行圆圈
them around
他们在周围
that right there is what we're looking
这就是我们要找的东西
for we want to make sure everything's
因为我们想确保每件事
covered here we don't have any of the
在这里，我们没有任何
main circles sticking out let me just
主圆突出，让我只想
zoom in to make sure
放大以确保
okay good we don't want any of that
好的，很好，我们不想要这些
and what i'm going to do now is if you
我现在要做的是，如果你
notice over here there's little indents
注意，在这里有一些小的缩进
coming in from these circles so we're
来自这些圈子，所以我们
going to create those next
接下来我将创建这些
so let me go and take i'm going to start
所以让我走吧，我要开始了
with this circle right here
这个圆圈就在这里
to zoom in and out i'm holding ctrl and
要放大和缩小，请按住Ctrl键和
rolling up the mouse wheel
卷起鼠标滚轮
and to move them to move the page around
并移动它们以在页面周围移动
i'm pressing down the mouse wheel and
我正在按下鼠标滚轮，然后
moving the mouse
移动鼠标
i'm going to duplicate this by hitting
我要通过点击来复制这个
control d i'm going to make that red
控制d我要把它变成红色
and then i'm going to duplicate it again
然后我要再复制一次
by hitting control d and i'm going to
按下控制键d，我就会
make this one green
把这个改成绿色的
and let me just move this one over like
让我把这个移过去，就像这样
this and we're
这件事和我们
looking at the uh the area that's
看着，呃，那个区域
sticking out here the color of red
在这里突显出红色
that's sticking out that's what we want
这是突出的，这是我们想要的
to pay attention to
关注……
something like that right there is what
像这样的东西就在那里
i'm looking for i'm going to hold shift
我在找我要轮班
click on the red circle behind it so we
点击它后面的红色圆圈，这样我们就可以
have both of these selected and go to
选择这两个选项，然后转到
path
路径
difference now i want to do the same
现在不同了，我想要做同样的事情
thing for all of the circles at the top
上面的所有圆圈都是这样的
here so let me zoom in so i can see this
在这里，让我放大，这样我就可以看到这个
a little better
稍微好一点
i want to move this circle over so that
我想把这个圆圈移过去，这样
it's intersecting with this area a
它与这一区域相交
little more so let me duplicate this by
再多一点，让我重复一下
hitting ctrl d
按下Ctrl%d
make that red duplicate it again make it
再做一次红色复制，再做一次
green
绿色
and i'll move this one out here like
我会把这个搬到这里来，就像
this
这
and one thing i'm looking for when i do
当我这样做的时候，我想要做的一件事
this i want to make sure if you notice
我想确认一下你是否注意到了
the tip
小费
of the uh the red crescent here is going
这里的红新月会
over the red crescent over here that we
在这里的红新月上，我们
previously created we want to make sure
之前创建的我们希望确保
that those two things are intersecting
这两件事是相交的
and overlapping completely
并且完全重叠
you don't want to leave it like this
你不会想让它就这样离开的
where it's not going all the way through
在那里它不会一直走到
so that's one thing to keep in mind
所以这是需要牢记的一件事
while you're going about this
当你做这件事的时候
if you have to you can take this one
如果有必要的话，你可以拿这个。
hold shift click the one beneath it and
按住Shift键并单击其下方的键
then just click it again to get the
然后只需再次单击它即可获得
rotation handles and just rotate it
旋转手柄，只需旋转它
around
在附近
to position it in a better spot all
把它放在一个更好的位置
right so that that right there is good
好的，所以那里的那个是好的
how it is i'm going to hold shift
怎么回事，我要轮班了
click both of those and go to path
同时单击这两个选项，然后转到路径
difference there we go
不同的是，我们开始了
and maybe maybe i'll rotate these around
也许我可以把这些东西旋转一下
a little bit like that
有点像那样
and i'm gonna have to move this one i
我得把这一张移到
can tell already i'm gonna move this one
我已经知道我要搬这一辆了
up here
在这上面
again duplicate that make that red
再复制一次，让它变成红色
duplicate it again make it green
再复制一次，让它变成绿色
and i'm going to position this one like
我要把这个放在这样的位置
this
这
maybe over here like this
也许像这样在这里
again now this is not overlapping so
再说一次，这并不重叠，所以
what i want to do is move this
我想要做的就是把这个
down like that there we go that's what
这样下去，我们就这样走了，就是这样
i'm looking for now let me take those go
我正在寻找，现在让我带走那些
to path
至路径
difference again to select two objects
再次出现差异以选择两个对象
at the same time just holding shift
同时按住Shift键
and clicking each of them do the same
点击其中的每一个都可以完成相同的操作
thing over here ctrl d
这里的东西ctrl d
we're pretty much just repeating this
我们几乎是在重复这一点
process over and over again until we get
一遍又一遍地处理，直到我们得到
to the
发送到
end of the exhaust plume here
排气烟流的末端在这里
that's good
那很好
oops did i miss that there we go and
哦，我是不是错过了我们要去的地方
we'll do the same thing over here
我们会在这里做同样的事情
you know i'm going to rotate this around
你知道我要把这个转过来
a little bit
有一点
yeah maybe i'll rotate it around some
好的，也许我会绕着它转几圈
more like that oops
更像是那个哦
okay that's good and then finally this
好的，很好，最后是这个
last one over here i'm going to
这里的最后一个我要去
just adjust that a little bit duplicate
把那个稍微调整一下就行了
that
那
make that red duplicate it again make it
再做一次红色复制，再做一次
green
绿色
and there we go path difference
这就是我们的路径差异
okay so we have this set in place now
好的，我们现在把这个布景准备好了
what i want to do now is
我现在想做的是
if you notice the areas where the red
如果你注意到红色区域
crescents the tips of them are sticking
新月，它们的尖端粘在一起
out from each other i just want to go
彼此分开，我只想离开
and manually
和手动
remove those from certain areas so i'm
把它们从某些区域移走，这样我就
going to remove this area from this
我要把这个区域从这里移走
crescent here to do that i'm going to
新月会来做这件事，我要
grab the bezier pen
拿起贝塞尔钢笔
which is over here you can press b on
在这里，你可以按b键。
the keyboard i'm going to create
我要创建的键盘
an object going around the tip of that
一个物体绕着它的尖端转
crescent right there
新月就在那里
grab the select tool hold shift click on
抓住选择工具按住Shift键并单击
the red shape and go to path
红色形状并转到Path
difference and i'll do the same thing
不同，我也会做同样的事情
over here back to the bezier pen
在这里回到贝塞尔笔下
i'm just going to press b on the
我只需按下b键
keyboard it's easier to do it that way
键盘，这样做更容易
back to the starting point back to the
回到起点回到起点
select tool for that we press s on the
为了选择工具，我们按下了S在
keyboard
键盘
hold shift path difference
按住Shift路径差
and i'll go over here and do the same
我会走到这里，做同样的事情
thing let me get rid of the uh
事情让我摆脱了那个
this area right here path
这片区域就在这条小路上
difference
差异
oops path
OOPS路径
difference there we go and then i'll
不同的是，我们走了，然后我
delete this part right here so let me
就在这里删除这部分，让我
grab the bezier pen again
再次抓起贝塞尔钢笔
bring this through like that
像这样把这个拿过来
back to the select tool actually no this
返回到选择工具实际上不是这个
one right here
一张就在这里
path difference there we go
路径差，我们开始了
okay so now i want to take all of the
好的，现在我想把所有的
red objects right here i'm just going to
红色物体就在这里，我只是要
click on one of them
点击其中一个
and go to edit select same
然后转到编辑选择相同
fill color and that's going to select
填充颜色，这将选择
all of the red objects right there and
所有的红色物体都在那里
go to
去
path union and now i want to unify
路径联盟，现在我想要统一
all of the green circles together so let
所有的绿色圆圈都在一起，所以让
me click on the green circle and go to
我点击绿色圆圈，然后转到
edit
编辑
select same fill color and go to
选择相同的填充颜色并转到
path union okay so what i want to do now
PATH UNION好的，我现在想做的是
is create an offset
是创建偏移量
of this um this green
这个这个绿色的
cloud right here so to do that i'm just
云就在这里，所以为了做到这一点，我只是
going to press ctrl d
正在按Ctrl d键
on the keyboard to duplicate that i'm
在键盘上复制我的声音
going to make this blue
我要让这一切变蓝
and i'm going to lower this beneath the
我要把这个放在下面
other two objects we just created so
我们刚刚创建的另外两个对象
come up here where it says lower
到这里来，上面写着放低一点
selection one step i'll click that once
选择一步我会点击一次
and then twice we want it to go beneath
然后两次我们想让它沉入海底
the red and the green objects and then
红色和绿色的物体，然后
go to
去
path and we're looking for dynamic
路径，我们正在寻找动态的
offset
偏移量
and once we get dynamic offset we're
一旦我们得到动态补偿，我们就
going to take this little node right
我要把这个小节点拿对了
here and just bring this out like that
这里，就像这样把这个拿出来
maybe about that much that's a good
也许差不多那么多，这是一个很好的
amount of padding right there so we'll
填充量就在那里，所以我们将
go to
去
path object to path to to finalize that
Path对象指向的路径，以最终确定
we're going to what i'm going to create
我们要去做我要做的事
now is the exhaust trail coming from the
现在是尾气的痕迹来自
rocket let me show you here this little
火箭，让我给你展示一下这个小东西
stream this little jet stream coming
这股小小的喷流来了
from the rocket that's going to be the
从火箭，这将是
next
下一首
thing that we create so let's move this
我们创造的东西，所以让我们移动这个
off to the side a little bit again to
再往边上移一点，
move the page around just
只需移动页面即可
pressing down the mouse wheel and moving
按下鼠标滚轮并移动
the mouse i'm going to grab the
我要抓的那只老鼠
rectangles tool right here
矩形工具就在这里
create a rectangle like this make this
像这样创建一个矩形，制作这个
green because we want that to match this
绿色，因为我们想让它与这个相匹配
green here
这里是绿色的
and now i'm going to grab the circles
现在我要抓起圆圈
and ellipses tool and make another
和省略号工具，并制作另一个
make a an ellipse going over it like
在上面画一个椭圆，就像这样
that now let me make that red so we can
现在让我把它染成红色，这样我们就可以
see it
看到了吗？
grab the select tool
抓起选择工具
duplicate this shape by pressing ctrl d
按Ctrld复制此形状
and then hold ctrl and click and drag
，然后按住ctrl键并单击并拖动。
this off to the right over here
这个就在这里右边
and what we're paying attention to is
我们关注的是
the intersecting area between
之间的相交区域
uh or the absent area between the two
呃，或者是两者之间的缺失区域
red red circles here this green
红红的圆圈在这里，这是绿色
object is what's going to be what
对象是将要成为的东西
remains so let me bring this down a
所以让我把这个放下来
little bit
一点点
this is going to be our little jet
这将是我们的小飞机
stream right here so
就在这里流淌，所以
i think that looks good right there so
我认为这看起来很好，所以
i'm going to hold shift click both red
我要按住Shift键并单击两个红色
circles go to
圈子转到
path union hold shift click on the green
路径联合按住Shift键并单击绿色
rectangle and go to path
矩形并转到路径
difference and what i'm going to do now
区别和我现在要做的
is create
是在创建
some empty space in the middle of it
中间有一些空地
like you see right here
就像你在这里看到的
so to do that let me duplicate this ctrl
要做到这一点，让我复制这个ctrl
d i'll make this red i'm going to bring
我要把这个染成红色，我要带上
this in a little bit
这是一个小问题
bring this side in a little bit bring
把这一边弄进来一点，把
this in some more like that
这个更像那个
move this over that's looking pretty
把这个挪过去，看起来很漂亮
good
好的
now let me hold shift and click on both
现在，我按住Shift键并单击这两个按钮
of those so we have them both selected
所以我们把他们都选了
and where it says align we're gonna go
上面写着我们要去的地方
to our align menu and click on
到我们的ALIGN菜单，然后点击
uh center on vertical axis like that and
呃，像这样在垂直轴上居中
now i'm just gonna take this
现在我要拿着这个
maybe bring this down a little bit bring
可能会把这个放低一点，
this up a little bit so that
把这个稍微抬高一点，这样
it sticks out from the edges there and
它从那里的边缘伸出，
then select them both
然后把它们都选上
and go to path difference
然后转到路径差
and now we have our little jet stream so
现在我们有了我们的小喷流，所以
let me hold ctrl and just scale this
让我按住Ctrl键并进行缩放
down
降下来
let me put this in place over here with
让我把这个放在这里
the rest of the design
设计的其余部分
that's looking pretty good i'm going to
那看起来很不错，我要去
hold shift click on the circle so we can
按住Shift键单击圆圈，这样我们就可以
center this up on our emblem here
把这个放在我们的会徽上
there we go click off of that to
好了，我们来点击一下
deselect everything now i'm going to
取消选择所有内容，现在我要
take this
拿着这个
and i'm going to lower it beneath the
我要把它降到下面
cloud here so i'm going to click this
云在这里，所以我要点击这个
button that says lower selection one
显示较低选择一的按钮
step
步骤
one two three we want it going beneath
一、二、三，我们要它沉到下面去
the blue object there but above the
蓝色物体在那里，但在
black circle here so let me zoom back
这里有个黑色圆圈，让我把它放大
out
输出
this time we're going to use a different
这一次，我们将使用不同的
approach for creating the offset we're
创建我们的偏移量的方法
going to use a stroke this time because
这次我要用一个笔划，因为
of the way that this
这件事的方式
object is structured so let me duplicate
对象是结构化的，所以让我复制
this object by hitting ctrl d
通过按ctrl d键创建此对象
i'm going to make this blue and then
我要把它弄成蓝色然后
give it a blue stroke by holding shift
通过按住Shift键对其进行蓝色描边
and clicking on the color blue
然后点击蓝色
and i'm going to lower that down until
我要把它降下来，直到
it goes beneath the green
它在果岭下面
object there and i want to come over
在那里反对，我想过来
here to where it says stroke style
这里是笔画风格的地方
and just adjust the thickness of it here
然后在这里调整一下它的厚度
if you notice the thickness of the blue
如果你注意到蓝色的厚度
offset over here
偏移量在这里
we want this to be significantly thicker
我们希望这层要厚得多
than that
比那还多
so let me increase that a little bit
所以让我稍微增加一点
okay right about there that looks good
好的，就在那里，看起来不错。
you can just eyeball it that right there
你可以看着它就在那里
looks pretty good so i'm going to go
看起来很不错，所以我要走了
ahead and go to
继续前进并转到
path stroke to path path
路径笔划到路径路径
break apart we're going to ungroup this
分开，我们要把这个拆开
and then go to path union and the
然后转到Path Union和
ungroup is right here if you hover the
如果您将鼠标悬停在
cursor over the button it says
光标放在按钮上，上面写着
ungroup selected objects i just click it
取消对选定对象的分组我只需单击它
a couple of times just to make sure it's
几次，只是为了确保它
ungrouped
未分组
and now what we can do is i'm going to
现在我们能做的就是我要
take this blue object right here
把这个蓝色的物体拿在这里
i'm going to duplicate that by pressing
我要重复这一点，按下
ctrl d i'm going to hold shift
Ctrl d我要按住Shift
click on the green object right here and
点击此处的绿色对象，然后
go to path
转到路径
difference and if you notice we now have
如果你注意到我们现在有
that cut off there it's going to be
它将在那里被切断
separated from the cloud at the bottom
从底部的云中分离出来
there so
就是这样
that's why we did that now i'm going to
这就是我们这么做的原因现在我要
take the the black circle in the
把黑色的圆圈放在
background control d
后台控制%d
to duplicate that hold shift click on
要复制按住Shift键，请单击
the green cloud right there
就在那里的绿云
go to path intersection
转到路径交叉点
and then what i want to do is i want to
然后我想做的是我想要
take this blue object
拿着这个蓝色的物体
hold shift take this blue object and
按住Shift键拿起这个蓝色物体
then go to
然后转到
path union
路径并集
and then hold shift and click on the
然后按住Shift键并单击
black circle and go to
黑圈和转到
path difference and now we have that
路径差异，现在我们有了
there so let me go to
好了，让我去看看
now i'm going to go to path break apart
现在我要去Path Breakout
click off of the object to deselect
单击该对象以取消选择
everything and if you have this little
一切，如果你有这个小小的
center piece here in the middle you just
中间这一块，你只要
take that and get rid of it
拿着它，然后把它扔掉
so what i'm going to do now is i'm going
所以我现在要做的是我要去
to take this red object right here
把这个红色的物体放在这里
hold shift click on the green cloud and
按住Shift键并单击绿色云，然后
go to path
转到路径
difference and there we have the uh
不同的是，我们有呃
the exhaust with the um cloud plume
喷着乌云羽毛的废气
there
那里
so what we have to do now is let's we
所以我们现在要做的是让我们
can start we can actually start coloring
可以开始了吗？我们可以开始上色了
this in now so let me select all of this
这就是现在，让我选择所有这些
bring the opacity all the way up like
把不透明度一直调高，就像
that and i'm going to use a shade
我要用一种遮阳板
similar to what i used for the thumbnail
与我在缩略图中使用的类似
design like a dark purple
设计成深紫色
combined with a lighter shade of purple
加上较浅的紫色
like that
就像这样
there we go i'm going to take that i'm
我们走吧，我要带上它，我
just going to use the dropper to make
我要用滴管来做
that the same color
同样的颜色
there we go and now i'm going to put
好了，现在我要把
some stars in the background here to
背景中的一些明星在这里
make it look more like it's
让它看起来更像是
more like it's in space like that so go
更像是在太空中，所以去吧
ahead and grab the
走在前面，抓住
we're looking for the stars and polygons
我们在寻找星星和多边形
tool which is right here
就在这里的工具
for the settings we're going to want
对于我们想要的设置
this one selected right here that says
这张选在这里，上面写着
star instead of regular polygon we're
我们是星形而不是正多边形
going to want four corners
我想要四个角
spoke ratio 0.401
轮辐比0.401
and then rounded and randomized both set
然后取整和随机化两组
to zero i'm just going to hold ctrl and
设置为零，我只需按住Ctrl键并
shift and create our little star like
改变和创造我们的小星星就像
that
那
i'm going to get rid of that stroke or
我要摆脱中风，要不
that blue outline by holding
拿着那蓝色的轮廓线
shift and clicking on this little red x
按住Shift键并单击这个红色的小x
down here
在这下面
and i'll take this and just bring this
我要拿着这个，拿着这个
over here like this scale it down so it
在这里，像这样把它缩小，这样它
fits
配合
i'll make this white and i'll just add a
我会把它改成白色，我只需要添加一个
few of these in here
这里几乎没有这样的东西
at different sizes to make it look more
不同的大小，使它看起来更
natural
天然的
if you'll make this one a little bigger
如果你能把这件做大一点
like that there we go and i'll put the
就像这样，我们走了，我会把
same thing over here on this side so
在这边也是一样，所以
i'll just select all four of those
我就把这四个都选了
hit ctrl d to duplicate and then flip
按Ctrld复制，然后翻转
them horizontally
它们是水平的
with this button up here and then just
把这个按钮放在这里，然后就
move these over here like that
把这些像那样搬到这里来
and there we go so now we have the stars
我们走了，所以现在我们有了星星
set in place so the final step now
就位，所以现在是最后一步
is to create the little rocket at the
就是创造出一枚小型火箭
top of the design here so to do that
在这个设计的顶端，这样做
let's come over here to the side i'm
我们到这边来吧，我在
going to grab the circles and ellipses
去抓圆圈和椭圆形
tool hold ctrl and shift and click and
工具按住Ctrl和Shift并单击和
drag to create a perfectly round circle
拖动可创建一个完美的圆形
and showing up as white on my screen so
在我的屏幕上显示为白色，所以
once you've done that you'll have to
一旦你这样做了，你就必须
change it to a different color like
换成不同的颜色，就像
black
黑色
bring the opacity down in half grab the
将不透明度降低一半，抓起
select tool
选择工具
duplicate it with ctrl d and just hold
用ctrld复制，然后按住
ctrl and bring this over like this what
按住Ctrl键把这个像这样拿过来怎么样？
we're looking at here
我们现在看到的是
is the intercepting area between these
是它们之间的拦截区域吗？
two circles
两个圆圈
that's going to make up the top of the
那将会是最顶端的
rocket so let me select both of those
火箭，所以让我来选择这两个
and go to path intersection
然后走到小路交叉口
and now i'm going to create the little
现在我要创造一个小小的
fins on the side so to do that i'm
把鳍放在边上，所以我是
actually going to create a triangle so
实际上要创建一个三角形，所以
to create a triangle
创建三角形的步骤
i'm going to grab this the squares and
我要把这个拿到正方形和
rectangles tool
矩形工具
control and shift to create a perfectly
按住Ctrl键和Shift键可以完美地创建
symmetrical square like that
像这样对称的正方形
make sure it has sharp corners by
确保它有尖锐的边角
clicking that button right there if
如果出现以下情况，请单击此处的按钮
it's not if you're not able to click
如果你不能点击就不会了
that button that means you already have
这个按钮意味着你已经有了
sharp corners you're good to go
急转弯，你可以走了
convert that to a path by going to path
通过转到路径将其转换为路径
object to path
对象到路径
grab the nodes tool and then just take
抓起节点工具，然后只需
this node right here in the bottom right
右下角的这个节点
and press delete on the keyboard to get
并按键盘上的Delete键以获取
rid of it
把它扔掉
now select all three of these nodes and
现在选择所有这三个节点，然后
come up here to where it says
到上面写着的地方来
make selected nodes corner
使选定节点成为角点
like that go back to the select tool
就像这样，返回到选择工具
click on the object again so we get the
再次单击该对象，这样我们就可以看到
rotation handles and i'm going to hold
旋转手柄，我要拿着
ctrl and just rotate this counter
按住Ctrl键并旋转此计数器
clockwise like this
像这样顺时针方向
so that it's sitting up like that i'm
所以它就这样坐着，我是
going to position this over here next to
我要把这个放在这里旁边
the side of the rocket
火箭的一侧
you can click on it again to get the
您可以再次单击它以获取
scaling handles i'm just going to scale
伸缩手柄我只是要伸缩
it so that it
它就是这样的
fits next to the uh the body of the
紧挨着，呃，身体旁边
rocket here
火箭在这里
now i just want to adjust this a little
现在我只想稍微调整一下这个
bit so i'm going to grab the nodes tool
所以我要抓起节点工具
over here
在这里
i'm just going to click and drag this
我只需要点击并拖动这个
node up here like this and maybe i'll
像这样在这里结点，也许我会
take this node and bring this over to
拿着这个节点，把这个带到
the left as well
左翼也是如此
bring this down a little bit maybe bring
把这个放低一点，也许会带来
that up
那就好了
you know what this needs to be down a
你知道这需要什么吗？
little more like that that looks better
再像那样一点，看起来更好
okay so now i'm just going to duplicate
好的，现在我要复制
that
那
ctrl d flip it horizontally
Ctrl%d水平翻转
hold ctrl click and drag it over here to
按住Ctrl键单击并将其拖到此处
the right
权利
and now we're going to unify both of
现在我们要把这两者统一起来
them together by holding shift and
通过按住Shift和
clicking on both of them so we have them
点击这两个按钮，我们就可以看到它们了
both selected and go to path
选择并转到路径
union and now we can hold shift
联合，现在我们可以按住Shift
click on this little uh shape right here
点击这里的这个小的呃形状
center that up where it says a line
在上面写着一行字的地方居中
come over here to where it says center
到这里来，到它说中心的地方
on vertical axis
垂直轴上
make sure it's centered up go to path
确保它居中，转到路径
union
友联市
and now i'm just going to close off the
现在我要关闭
bottom over here i'm going to grab the
在这下面，我要拿起
rectangle tool and create a little
矩形工具，并创建一个小
rectangle going over the bottom there
长方形在底部
grab the select tool hold
抓住选择刀柄
shift click on the rocket and go to path
按住Shift键点击火箭并转到Path
union and now i'm just going to add a
UNION，现在我要添加一个
little circle right here for like a
小圆圈就在这里，就像一个
little
一点儿
i guess it's kind of like a little
我想这有点像是
window i'm going to put right there so
我要把窗户放在那里，所以
to do that
要做到这一点
i'm going to grab the circles and
我要抓起圆圈
ellipses tool hold ctrl and shift
椭圆工具按住Ctrl和Shift键
click and drag to create a perfectly
单击并拖动以创建完美的
round circle right there position that
圆圈就在那里，位置是
right about there
就在那里
or maybe right there select both of
或者就在那里，同时选择两个
those
那些
and center them up on the vertical axis
并使它们在垂直轴上居中
then duplicate this circle take that
然后复制这个圆圈，拿那个
ctrl d let me zoom in a little bit
Ctrl d让我放大一点
there we go take the larger circle hold
我们去拿更大的圆圈
shift
换班
and select the rocket as well go to path
并选择火箭也去路径
difference there we go now we have our
不同的是，我们现在走了，我们有了
window set
窗套装
let me select both of those and go to
让我选择这两个选项，然后转到
path union
路径并集
and now our rocket is set we just need
现在我们的火箭已经准备好了，我们只需要
to place it over the design over here so
把它放在这里的设计上，这样
to do this i'm just going to place it
要做到这一点，我只需要把它放在
over here
在这里
i'm going to hold ctrl scale it down a
我要按住Ctrl键，把它缩小到
bit
比特
let's unify these two objects right here
让我们将这两个对象统一在这里
the sky let's take this guy
天空，让我们带上这个家伙
hold shift take the other side of the
按住Shift键走另一边
sky and go to path
天空和转到路径
union because i want to make sure that
联合，因为我想确保
this rocket is centered up on this
这枚火箭的中心是这个
design here so let me take the rocket
在这里设计，所以让我乘坐火箭
hold shift
按住Shift键
click on the sky and then center it up
点击天空，然后将其居中
on the vertical axis like that
在这样的垂直轴上
just bring this down make it a little
把这个放下来，让它变得有点
smaller like that
像那样小一点
i'm going to bring the opacity all the
我要把所有的不透明带到
way up and i'm going to make it the same
我要让它变得和以前一样
color as the sky here so let me grab the
颜色就像这里的天空，所以让我抓住
dropper
滴管
and grab that sample selection now i
现在就拿起那个样品选择
want to create another offset of this to
要创建此的另一个偏移量以
put above the
放在上面
jet stream here so to do that ctrl d
Jet Stream在这里，这样做ctrl d
make this white hold shift click on
使此白色按住Shift键单击打开
white again to give this a white stroke
再白一次，给这个白色的笔划
and then lower this lower selection one
然后再降低这个下部的选择
step to put it beneath
一步一步把它放在下面
the rocket there and come over here to
火箭在那里，到这里来
the stroke style tab again
再次使用笔划样式选项卡
and adjust the width of this so that's
并调整这个的宽度，这样就可以
not quite
不完全是
as wide
一样宽
i'm just going to go ahead and position
我现在要做的就是
this where i'd like it to be maybe down
我想把它放在这里，也许是向下的
a little more
再多一点
that's pretty good right there so once
这就很好，就这么一次
we've done that you can click off it to
我们已经做到了这一点，您可以点击它
deselect everything
取消选择所有内容
click on the white don't click on the
点击白色，不要点击
rocket click on the white object beneath
火箭点击下方的白色物体
the rocket and go to path
火箭和去路径
stroke to path path break apart
笔划到路径路径断开
ungroup and go to path
取消分组并转到路径
union and now i'm going to hold shift
工会，现在我要换班了
click on the jet stream and go to path
点击喷流并转到路径
difference and then path break apart
差异，然后路径分裂
click off it to deselect we can get rid
单击该选项以取消选择我们可以摆脱
of these objects now just press delete
现在只需按Delete即可
on the keyboard to get rid of them
在键盘上除掉它们
zoom back out and as you can see we are
缩小后，如您所见，我们正在
finished we have created
完成我们已经创建的
our rocket logo design with inkscape if
我们的火箭标志设计与Inkscape IF
you want now you can go ahead and add
你想要现在你可以继续添加
some text if you'd like otherwise you
一些文本，如果你愿意的话，否则你
can just export this design and use it
我可以只导出此设计并使用它
as you'd like so
如你所愿
if you have any questions leave a
如果您有任何问题，请在
comment below and as always thanks for
在下面发表评论，并一如既往地感谢
[Music]
[音乐]
watching
观看